[
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "major1",
    "a1": "Minor 7th",
    "a2": "Major 7th",
    "a3": "Dominant 7th",
    "a4": "Diminished 7th",
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "minor1",
    "a1": "Augmented 7th",
    "a2": "Dominant 7th",
    "a3": "Major 7th",
    "a4": "Minor 7th",
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "diminished1",
    "a1": "Major 7th",
    "a2": "Minor 7th",
    "a3": "Diminished 7th",
    "a4": "Dominant 7th",
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "augmented1",
    "a1": "Minor 7th",
    "a2": "Augmented 7th",
    "a3": "Major 7th",
    "a4": "Diminished 7th",
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "major2",
    "a1": "Major 7th",
    "a2": "Dominant 7th",
    "a3": "Diminished 7th",
    "a4": "Minor 7th",
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "diminished2",
    "a1": "Major 7th",
    "a2": "Augmented 7th",
    "a3": "Minor 7th",
    "a4": "Diminished 7th",
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "minor2",
    "a1": "Minor Seventh",
    "a2": "Diminished 7th",
    "a3": "Dominant 7th",
    "a4": "Major 7th",
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "minor3",
    "a1": "Dominant 7th",
    "a2": "Augmented 7th",
    "a3": "Minor 7th",
    "a4": "Diminished 7th",
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "dominant1",
    "a1": "Diminished 7th",
    "a2": "Major 7th",
    "a3": "Dominant 7th",
    "a4": "Minor 7th",
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "augmented2",
    "a1": "Dominant 7th",
    "a2": "Minor 7th",
    "a3": "Major 7th",
    "a4": "Augmented 7th",
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "dominant2",
    "a1": "Major 7th",
    "a2": "Dominant 7th",
    "a3": "Minor 7th",
    "a4": "Diminished 7th",
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of 7th chord is this?",
    "interval": "minor4",
    "a1": "Minor 7th",
    "a2": "Major 7th",
    "a3": "Augmented 7th",
    "a4": "Dominant 7th",
    "correct": "1"
  }
]